

# Avijit Mondal iOS Engineer

## **My Contact**

avijitmobi@gmail.com

+91 8016605258

• Medinipur, West Bengal

https://avijit.ml

#### **Skills Summary**

- iOS Development with Swift
- iOS Development with Obj C
- iOS Own Frameworks
- Realtime Database Firebase
- Android Development with Kotlin
- Object Oriented Programming

# Extra Activity / Hobby

- Editing Videos
- Traveling
- Sketch-board Animation

### **Education Background**

 Jalpaiguri Govt. Engg. College Bachelor of Technology Completed in 2018

Jhakra High School
Class V to Higher Secondary Education
2007 - 2014

#### **About Me**

I am an iOS Engineer. I have spent more than one year in the IT industry and upgraded my skill as much as I can with my dedication and hard work and time. I am an iOS Developer. I have spent more than one year in the IT industry and upgraded my skill as much as I can with my dedication and hard work and time.

#### **Professional Experience**

CodelogicX Technology Pvt. Ltd. | iOS Engineer July 2021 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Implement many projects with our teams, gained more knowledge, and learned team-working.
- Start to manage projects with git.
- Built various types of apps like shopping, quiz, scanner, payment etc.

Convergent Infoware Pvt. Ltd. | iOS Developer Jan 2019 - July 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Start development in iOS development with Obj-C and Swift.
- Done 4 projects from scratch to end with my own.
- Gained pretty much knowledge on AutoLayout, Navigation stacks, Tabs, Gesture Recogniser, etc.

### **Recent Projects**



Popping is a social media app where users can ping any status for a Hub. <u>Click here</u> to see the project in detail.



Sama Contact Lens is an e-commerce app for selling Contact Lens in Dubai. <u>Click here</u> to see the project in detail.



Aswagna is an e-commerce app where users can shop anything in Kuwait. <u>Click here</u> to see the project in detail.